U.S. Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations (Dunlop Commission) Documents 6220
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILR Catherwood Library Hot Topic: "Future Worker" documents from January, 1995, 1994; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: News: Report and Recommendation of the Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations Released Today, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Author: Liz Rose; Stephen Gaskill
    Notes: January 9, 1995.
  - Item 4: Statement of Fred Feinstein concerning Dunlop Commission Report, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Statement of William B. Gould IV concerning Dunlop Commission Report, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Dunlop Report Picks Right Targets, But Falls Short, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Author: Candice Johnson; Mary McDonald
  - Item 7: LPA Reacts to Dunlop Commission Report, 1995; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Author: Meghan Clendenny